Irma Kalish Scripts and Videos
Irma Kalish Scripts and Videos
1954-1990
Kalish, Irma
14 linear ft.
Scripts and videorecordings of television shows written and/or produced by Irma Kalish. Collection includes many of scripts done with her partner Rocky Kalish. Television shows represented include Family Affair, My Three Sons, F-Troop, Bob Newhart, Maude, and The Brian Keith Show
2524345
Biographical History
Irma Kalish is a Phi Beta Kappa graduate of Syracuse University and one of television's most talented writers/producers. Kalish began her career as a writer shortly after graduating from Syracuse University when she was hired to produce stories for a New York City magazine. By 1950, she and her husband, Austin "Rocky" Kalish, had moved to Los Angeles and had begun collaborating on radio scripts for the Dean Martin and Jerry Lewis Hour. When the Martin and Lewis show switched to television, the Kalishes followed and launched their careers as television writers at a time when few women were writing comedy.
As a team, the Kalishes have created more than 300 scripts for television shows such as All in the Family, Bob Newhart, F-Troop, Family Affair, I Dream of Jeannie, The Love Boat, Maude, My Three Sons and The Brian Keith Show. In their earlier years, they wrote scripts for shows such as The Ray Milland Show and Gunsmoke. Their credits also include writing the pilot episode of Gilligan's Island, producing Too Close for Comfort and Good Heavens, and writing and producing the full-length film Keep Off My Grass. More recently, Ms. Kalish has worked on her own as the chief writer for 227 and executive producer of The Facts of Life. With her work for Good Times, she became the first woman to be made producer and eventually executive producer of a television series.
Beyond her direct involvement in television production and writing, Kalish has been active in a number of related organizations, particularly with respect to women's issues. Kalish is an active member and past president of Women in Film and past chair of their WIF Foundation. She is also a founding member of Women & Science, affiliated with the Weizmann Institute of Science in Rehovot, Israel, and an executive member of the Association for Women in Communications, a professional organization that champions the advancement of women across all communications disciples. She has been a board member of the Motion Picture and Television Fund for 22 years, serving on a number of committees (including the Executive Committee of their Samuel Goldwyn Foundation Child Care Center) and chairing their Accreditation and Quality Assurance Committee. She has been an active member of the Writers Guild of America (West) since 1964, serving on or chairing many of their committees; she is presently on the board of directors for the guild.
Kalish's efforst have been recognized many times over the years. She was twice recognized for her work by the Writers Guild of America with their Morgan Cox Award (1993) and the Valentine Davies Award (2005). Women in Film's WIF Foundation presented her with their Founders Award in 1997, and the Association for Women in Communications awarded her both its National Headliner and Far West Woman of Achievement Awards. Syracuse University awarded her their highest alumni honor, the George Arents Pioneer Medal.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Irma Kalish Scripts and Videos consists of material from popular television shows from the 1970s and 1980s that were written and/or produced by Kalish. Shows with a significant number of Scripts include 227, the Brian Keith Show, Facts of Life, Family Affair, Good Times, Heaven Help Us, Hogan Family, and My Three Sons. Videos comprises VHS tapes of episodes of 227 (6 tapes), Hogan Family (11 tapes), and Sugar & Spice (8 tapes).
Arrangement of the Collection
Both Scripts and Videos are arranged alphabetically by show title, and within that by air date.
Related Material
has several other collections of television scripts and videos. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Radio, television, film; Popular culture; Kalish, Irma; 227 (television series); Brian Keith show (television series); F-troop (television series); Facts of life (television series); Family affair (television series); Good times (television series); Heaven help us (television series); Hogan family (television series); My three sons (television series); Popular culture -- United States.; Television -- United States.; Television comedies -- United States.; Television series.; Shooting scripts.; Videotapes.; Television comedy writers.; Television producers and directors.; Women television producers and directors.; Women television writers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Access to recordings requires advance notice to produce a use copy.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Irma Kalish.
Inventory
- Scripts
  - 227
    See also Videos: 227, below.
    - 0410 - Night They Arrested Santa - Final Draft, 12/5/88 (Box 1)
    - 0411 - Real Decoys - Final Draft, 12/12/88 (Box 1)
    - 0412 - A Class Act, 1/9/89 (Box 1)
    - 0413 - Prince, 1/17/89 (Box 1)
    - 0414 - Babes in the Woods, 1/23/89 (Box 1)
    - 0415 - Mary's Cookies, 2/6/89 (Box 1)
    - 0416 - A Date to Remember, 2/13/89 (Box 1)
    - 0417 - For Richer, For Poorer, 2/21/89 (Box 1)
    - 0418 - Class of '89, 3/6/89 (Box 1)
    - 0419 - Trial & Error, 3/13/89 (Box 1)
    - 0420 - Bet, 3/20/89 (Box 1)
    - 0421 - House Number, 3/27/89 (Box 1)
    - 0422 - No...My Darling Daughter, 4/10/89 (Box 1)
    - 0423 - For Sale, 4/24/89 (Box 1)
    - 0501 - Fight of the Century - Tue. Tape Script, 8/8/89 (Box 1)
    - 0502 - Pampered Tale - Tue. Tape Script, 8/15/89 (Box 1)
    - 0503 - Take My Diva...Please! - Tue. Tape Script, 8/22/89 (Box 2)
    - 0504 - Tenants, Anyone? - Tue. Tape Script, 9/6/89 (Box 2)
    - 0505 & 0506 - How the West was Fun I & II - Tue. Final/Location., 9/12/89 (Box 2)
    - 0505 & 0506 - How the West was Fun I & II - Tue. Tape Script, 9/12/89 (Box 2)
    - 0506 - How the West was Fun II - Final Draft, 9/12/89 (Box 2)
    - 0507 - There Go the Clowns - Tue. Tape Script, 10/3/89 (Box 2)
    - 0508 - War is Heck - Tue. Tape Script, 10/10/89 (Box 2)
    - 0509 - Flying Down to Leo's - Tue. Tape Script, 10/17/89 (Box 2)
    - 0510 - Video-Activity - Tue. Tape Script, 10/31/89 (Box 2)
    - 0511 - Reunion Blues - Tue. Tape Script, 11/7/89 (Box 2)
    - 0512 - Perfume Game - Tue. Tape Script, 11/14/89 (Box 2)
    - 0513 - Gone Fishing - Tue. Tape Script, 11/21/89 (Box 2)
    - 0514 - Come the Revolution - Tue. Tape Script, 12/5/89 (Box 2)
    - 0515 - Guess Who's Not Coming to Xmas - Tue. Tape, 12/12/89 (Box 2)
    - 0516 - Where Do We Go From Here? - Tue. Pre Tape, 12/19/89 (Box 2)
    - 0517 - Play Christie For Me - Tue. Tape Script, 1/9/90 (Box 2)
    - 0518 - Knock it Off - Wed. Tape Script, 1/9/90 (Box 3)
    - 0519 - Do Not Pass Go I - Tue. Tape Script, 1/30/90 (Box 3)
    - 0520 - Do Not Pass Go II - Tue. Tape Script, 2/6/90 (Box 3)
    - 0521 - You Gotta Have Art - Tue. Tape Script, 2/13/90 (Box 3)
    - 0522 - No Place Like Home - Tue. Tape Script, 2/27/90 (Box 3)
    - 0523 - Nightmare On '227' - Tue. Tape Script, 3/6/90 (Box 3)
    - 0524 - Class of '90 - Tue. Tape Script, 3/13/90 (Box 3)
  - All in the Family
    - Blockbuster, 9/24/71 (Box 3)
    - Gloria the Victim, 4/10/72 (Box 3)
    - Archie Goes Too Far, 1/12/73 (Box 3)
  - Anna and the King of Siam
    - Anna and the King of Siam - Shooting Final, 10/11/71 (Box 3)
    - Marriage of Prine Chula - Final, 7/10/72 (Box 3)
    - King or the Tiger? - Revised Final, 7/10/72 (Box 3)
    - Baby, 7/18/72 (Box 3)
    - Anna's Romance, 7/20/72 (Box 3)
    - Bicycle, 8/1/72 (Box 3)
    - Haunted Temple, 8/9/72 (Box 3)
    - Chulalongkorn's Grades, 8/21/72 (Box 3)
    - Louis, the Pawn, 8/22/72 (Box 3)
    - King and the Egg, 8/29/72 (Box 4)
    - Malee, 8/30/72 (Box 4)
    - Chimes, 9/7/72 (Box 4)
    - Serana, 9/11/72 (Box 4)
    - Louis' Love, 9/18/72 (Box 4)
  - Anne's World
    - Series Proposal for Anne Meara (Box 4)
  - Apple'sWay
    - 38222 - Circus, 7/5/74 (Box 4)
  - Beachcomber
    - Paradise Lost, 1/20/61 (Box 4)
  - Bewitched
    - Behind Every Man... - Revised, 4/28/64 (Box 4)
  - Big Breakthrough
    - Rough Draft, 9/28/82 (Box 4)
  - Bob Newhart Show
    - 7274 - Bum Voyage, 1/25/73 (Box 4)
    - Requiem for a Rabbit - First Draft, 7/9/73 (Box 4)
  - Brian Keith Show
    - Austin Moves In - Final Draft, 7/23/73 (Box 4)
    - Camp Doctor - Final Draft, 7/25/73 (Box 4)
    - Sean, The Allergist - Final Draft, 7/27/73 (Box 4)
    - Doctor Chaffee, I Presume? - Rev. Final Draft, 7/30/73 (Box 4)
    - Pineapple League - Final Draft, 8/2/73 (Box 4)
    - Sunday, Fishy Sunday - Final Draft, 8/7/73 (Box 4)
    - Inflation - Final Draft, 8/8/73 (Box 4)
    - New Bathroom - Final Draft, 8/13/73 (Box 4)
    - Sean, the Swinger - Final Draft, 8/14/73 (Box 4)
    - Here Comes the What? - Final Draft, 8/31/73 (Box 4)
    - Uncle Timothy - Final Draft, 9/7/73 (Box 5)
    - A House Call is Not a Home - Final Draft, 9/12/73 (Box 5)
    - Thunderball Syndicate - Final Draft, 9/21/73 (Box 5)
    - Doctor, Take Five - Final Draft, 10/2/73 (Box 5)
    - No Man is an Atoll - Final Draft, 10/3/73 (Box 5)
    - A Star is Sean - Final Draft, 10/15/73 (Box 5)
    - Titanic Sails Again - Revised Final Draft, 10/16/73 (Box 5)
    - Sean-Do the Magician - Final Draft & Revisions, 10/18/73 (Box 5)
    - Make Room for Sean - Final Draft & Revisions, 10/24/73 (Box 5)
    - Sean, the Dad - Final Draft, 10/29/73 (Box 5)
    - New Doctor in Town - Final Draft, 11/6/73 (Box 5)
    - Play it Again, Sean - Final Draft, 11/8/73 (Box 5)
    - Ultra-Marine - Final Draft, 11/9/73 (Box 5)
  - Cimarron Strip
    - 0718 - Heller, 11/8/67 (Box 5)
  - Come Out of the Bathroom, Hannibal Fry
    - Original (Box 5)
    - Revised, 139 pp. (Box 6)
    - Revised, 128 pp. (Box 6)
  - Cookie's Place
    - Robbery (Box 6)
  - Diane
    - Pilot Script - second revised draft, 12/29/75 (Box 6)
  - Dusty's Trail
    - Half Moon - Final Draft, 6/6/73 (Box 6)
    - Cavalry's Coming - Final Draft, 8/14/73; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Elroy
    - Presentation Notes (Box 6)
  - F-Troop
    - Those Ungeschik Men in Their Flying Machines - Final Script, 6/16/66 (Box 6)
    - Battle of Corporal Agarn - Final Script, 8/22/66 (Box 6)
    - Mondo Courage - Final Script, 9/14/66 (Box 6)
    - Our Brave in F-Troop - Final Script, 10/18/66 (Box 6)
    - What Are You Doing After the Massacre? - Revised Draft, 11/9/66 (Box 6)
    - V is for Vampire - Revised Draft, 11/30/66 (Box 7)
    - Day They Shot Agarn - Revised Draft, 12/15/66 (Box 7)
    - Is This Fort Really Necessary? - Final Draft, 1/25/67 (Box 7)
  - Facts of Life
    - 0806 - Write and Wrong - Final Draft, 9/2/86 (Box 7)
    - 0807 - Off-Broadway Baby - Final Draft, 10/14/86 (Box 7)
    - 0808 - Little Chill - Final Draft, 10/21/86 (Box 7)
    - 0809 - Ratings Game - Final Draft, 10/27/86 (Box 7)
    - 0810 - Fast Food - Final Draft, 11/29/86 (Box 7)
    - 0811 - Wedding Day - Final Draft, 11/22/86 (Box 7)
    - 0812 - Seven Little Indians - Final Draft, 11/25/86 (Box 7)
    - 0813 - Greek Connection - Final Draft, 12/9/86 (Box 7)
    - 0814 - A Winter's Tale - Final Draft, 12/16/86 (Box 7)
    - 0815 -Post-Christmas Card - Final Draft, 1/17/87 (Box 7)
    - 0816 - Star is Torn - Final Draft, 1/31/87 (Box 7)
    - 0817 - Cupid's Revenge - Final Draft, 2/14/87 (Box 7)
    - 0818 - Boy About the House - Final Draft, 2/28/87 (Box 7)
    - 0819 - '62 Pick-Up - Final Draft, 2/21/87 (Box 7)
    - 0820 - Ex Marks the Spot - Final Draft, 3/7/87 (Box 7)
    - 0821 - Younger Than Springtime - Final Draft, 3/21/87 (Box 8)
    - 0822 - This Is Only a Test - Final Draft, 3/17/87 (Box 8)
    - 0823 - Rights of Passage - Final Draft, 5/2/87 (Box 8)
    - 0824 - Rights of Passage, Too - Final Draft, 5/9/87 (Box 8)
    - 0901 - Rumor Has It - Final Draft, 6/2/87 (Box 8)
    - 0902 - A Rose By Any Other Age - Final Draft, 6/9/87 (Box 8)
    - 0903 - Down & Out in Malibu - Pt. 1 - Final Draft, 6/16/87 (Box 8)
    - 0904 - Down & Out in Malibu - Pt. 2 - Final Draft, 6/23/87 (Box 8)
    - 0905 - Before the Fall - Final Draft, 7/21/87 (Box 8)
    - 0906 - Golden Oldies - Final Draft, 7/28/87 (Box 8)
    - 0907 - Sweet Charity - Final Draft, 8/4/87 (Box 8)
    - 0908 - More the Marrier [sic] - Final Draft, 8/18/87 (Box 8)
    - 0909 - It's a Wonderful Christmas - Final Draft, 8/25/87 (Box 8)
    - 0910 - Up From Down Under - Final Draft, 9/1/87 (Box 8)
    - 0911 - A Thousand Frowns - Final Draft, 9/15/87 (Box 9)
    - 0912 - Adventures in Baileysitting - Final Draft, 9/22/87 (Box 9)
    - 0913 - A House Divided - Final Draft, 9/29/87 (Box 9)
    - 0914 - Less Than Perfect - Final Draft, 10/20/87 (Box 9)
    - 0915 - First Time - Final Draft, 10/27/87 (Box 9)
    - 0916 - Let's Face the Music - Final Draft, 11/10/87 (Box 9)
    - 0917 - Something in Common - Final Draft, 11/17/87 (Box 9)
    - 0918 - Peekskill Law - Final Draft, 11/24/87 (Box 9)
    - 0919 - On the Edge - Final Draft, 12/8/87 (Box 9)
    - 0920 - Present Imperfect - Final Draft, 12/15/87 (Box 9)
    - 0921 - Big Apple Blues - Final Draft, 1/19/88 (Box 9)
    - 0922 - Till Marriage Do Us Part - Final Draft, 2/27/88 (Box 9)
    - 0923 - Part 1: Beginning of the End, 2/11/88 (Box 9)
    - 0923 - Part 1: Beginning of the End - Final Draft, 2/12/88 (Box 9)
    - 0924 - Part 2: Beginning of the Beginning, 2/26/88 (Box 9)
    - 0924 - Part 2: Beginning of the Beginning - Final Draft, 3/2/88 (Box 10)
  - Family Affair
    - Unidentified Script (Box 10)
    - 5785-6 - Room with a ViewPoint, 6/30/66 (Box 10)
    - 5785-17 - One for the Little Boy, 8/19/66 (Box 10)
    - 5785-26 - Once in Love with Buffy, 11/17/66 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0101 - Young Man from Bolivia, 11/30/66 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0113 - First Love, 5/17/67 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0123 - Somebody Upstairs (Rev. 6/19/67, 7/11/67), 6/14/67 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0131 - Ciao Uncle Bill (Rev. 4/8/68), 3/6/68 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0144 - A Family Group, 4/16/68 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0149 - Family Plan, 4/30/68 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0157 - Young Man from Bolivia, 7/18/68 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0158 - Birthday Boy, 4/23/69 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0159 - Stowaway, 4/22/69 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0160 - Cissy's Apartment, 4/24/69; 5/29/69; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - 8022-0161 - Uncle Prince Charming, 4/22/69 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0162 - A Tale of Two Travels, 4/25/69 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0163 - Wings of an Angel, 4/24/69 (Box 10)
    - 8022-0164 - There Goes New York, 4/29/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0165 - Jody Affair, 4/30/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0166 - Wouldn't it Be Lov-er-ly, 5/3/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0167 - Language of Love, 5/5/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0168 - Old Cowhand, 5/5/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0169 - Inheritance, 5/7/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0170 - Grandpa, Sir, 5/8/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0171 - Mr. Osaki's Tree, 5/13/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0172 - Boys Against the Girls, 5/16/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0173 - Goodbye Harold, 5/27/69 (Box 11)
    - Shooting Schedule, 5/29/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0175 - Family in Paradise - Part I, 6/3/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0176 - Family in Paradise - Part II, 6/4/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0177 - No Uncle is an Island, 6/12/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0178 - Number One Boy, 6/13/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0180 - With This Ring, 7/2/69 (Box 11)
    - 8022-0179 - What's So Funny About a Broken Leg?, 6/30/69; 7/2/69; 2 copies (Box 11)
    - 8022-0183 - Angel in the Family, 8/26/69; 8/27/69 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0182 - Girl Graduate, 8/27/69 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0182 - Maudie, 8/27/69 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0184 - Meet Emily - First Draft, 3/31/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0185 - You Can Fight City Hall - First Draft, 3/31/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0186 - Eastward Ho -First Draft, 3/31/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0187 -Put Your Dreams Away - First Draft, 4/1/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0188 - Buffy's Fair Lady - First Draft, 4/8/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0189 - Stamp of Approval - First Draft, 4/13/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0190 Goodbye, Mrs. Beasley - First Draft, 4/15/70 (Box 12)
    - 2245-0195 Good Neighbors, 4/28/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0194 Class Clown - First Draft (Rev. 4/30/70), 4/29/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0192 - Feat of Clay - First Draft, 4/30/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0193 - Desert Isle - Manhattan Style - First Draft, 4/30/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0195 - Too Late, Too Soon - First Draft, 5/6/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0197 - Joiners, 5/7/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0198 - Littlest Exile, 5/8/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0199 - Nobody Here But Us Uncles, 5/26/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0200 - Wish You Were Here, 6/3/70 (Box 12)
    - 8022-0201 - Cinder-Emily, 6/3/70 (Box 13)
    - 8022-0202 - Return of Maudie, 6/10/70 (Box 13)
    - 8022-0203 - Unsinkable Mr. French, 6/15/70 (Box 13)
    - 8022-0204 - Travels with Cissy, 6/15/70 (Box 13)
    - 8022-0205 - It Can't Be Five Years, 6/17/70 (Box 13)
    - 8022-0206 - Say Unlce, 6/17/70 (Box 13)
    - 8022-0207 - Heroes Are Born, 6/29/70 (Box 13)
    - 8022-0191 - And Baby Makes Eight - First Draft, 4/17/70 (Box 13)
  - Flintstones
    - [no title] (Box 13)
  - Flying Nun
    - 3510 - Days of Nuns and Roses, 7/26/67 (Box 13)
    - 3530 - You Can't Get There From Here, 9/20/67 (Box 13)
  - Funny Face
    - A Crush On Sandy, 10/2/71 (Box 13)
  - Ghost of a Chance
    - Pilot Script - First Draft (Box 13)
    - Unidentified Notes (Box 13)
    - Promotional Brochure (Box 13)
    - Partial Script (Box 13)
    - Daily Production Records (Box 13)
    - Pilot Script - Second Draft, 10/2/79 (Box 13)
    - Pilot Commitment & Unidentified Script, 10/11/79 (Box 13)
    - Pilot Script - Revised Second Draft, 10/15/79 (Box 13)
    - Pilot Script - Revised Second Draft, 10/15/79 (Box 13)
    - Pilot Script - Original Revised Second Draft, 10/15/79 (Box 14)
    - 60181-039 - Pilot Script - Revised Final Draft, 11/7/79 (Box 14)
    - Research Notes, 11/8/79 (Box 14)
    - Inter-Office Memos, 11/9/79 (Box 14)
    - Haunted House is Not a Home (Box 14)
    - Haunted House is Not A Home - First Draft, 1/29/80 (Box 14)
    - A Haunted House is Not a Home - Original First Draft, 1/29/80 (Box 14)
    - A Haunted House is Not a Home - First Draft, 1/29/80 (Box 14)
  - Good Heavens
    - 162504 - Good Neighbor Maxine, 10/3/75 (Box 14)
    - 162513 - Jack the Ribber and Me - Fin. Draft & Notes, 10/6/75 (Box 14)
    - 162512 - Big Bust, 10/10/75 (Box 14)
    - 162515 - Sisters, 10/20/75 (Box 14)
    - 162516 - Big Break, 10/20/75 (Box 14)
    - 162508 - Butterfly, 11/12/75 (Box 14)
    - 162517 - Funny Fellow, 11/18/75 (Box 14)
  - Good Morning. Miss Bliss
    - Complete Script & Production Notes, 4/29/87 (Box 14)
  - Good Times
    - 0416 - Thelma's African Romance - Pt.2, 12/16/76 (Box 15)
    - 0417 - Hustle, 12/23/76 (Box 15)
    - 0418 - A Friend in Need 1977/78 (Box 15)
    - 0419 - A Stormy Relationship, 1/20/77 (Box 15)
    - 0420 - Florida & Carl, 1/27/77 (Box 15)
    - 0506 - Thelma Moves Out, 9/8/77 (Box 15)
    - 0507 - Willina, the Fuzz, 9/15/77 (Box 15)
    - 0508 - Wheels, 9/29/77 (Box 15)
    - 0509 - Bye, Bye, Bookman, 10/6/77 (Box 15)
    - 0510 - Thelma's Brief Encounter, 10/13/77 (Box 15)
    - 0511 - Requiem for a Wino, 10/20/77 (Box 15)
    - 0512 - I Had a Dream, 11/3/77 (Box 15)
    - 0513 - Willona's Mr. Right, 11/10/77 (Box 15)
    - 0514 - No More Mr. Nice Guy, 11/17/77 (Box 15)
    - 0515 - Penny's Christmas, 12/1/77 (Box 15)
    - 0516 - J.J. & the Boss' Daughter, 12/8/77 (Box 15)
    - 0517 - Where There's Smoke, 12/15/77 (Box 15)
    - 0518 - Boarder, 12/22/77 (Box 15)
    - 0519 - Something Old, Something New, 1/12/78 (Box 15)
    - 0520 - J.J.'s Condition, 1/19/78 (Box 15)
    - 0521 - Willona, the Other Woman, 1/26/78 (Box 16)
    - 0522 - Write On, Thelma, 2/9/78 (Box 16)
    - 0523 - Willona's New Job, 2/16/78 (Box 16)
    - 0524 - That's Entertainment, Evens Style, 2/23/78 (Box 16)
  - Grindl
    - Grindl's Windfall - Revised, 2/17/64 (Box 16)
  - Gunsmoke
    - 1615 - Trapnell's Son, 3/28/75 (Box 16)
  - Hannibal (alternate title: The Making of the Mayor"
    See also Zack.
    - Pilot Script - First Draft, 7/18/83 (Box 16)
    - Pilot Script - Revised First Draft, 8/29/83 (Box 16)
    - Working Scripts & Notes, 1/16/84; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - He & She
    - 1727-#0554 - One of Our Firemen is Missing - Second Revised Final Draft, 8/3/67 (Box 16)
  - Heaven Help Us
    - 162506 - Take Me Out to the Ball Game - Final Draft, 5/12/75; 2 copies (Box 17)
    - 162502 - Senor Somebody - Final Draft, 6/4/75 (Box 17)
    - 162505 - Superscoop - Final Draft, 6/13/75 (Box 17)
    - 162507 - A Night With Brockton - Final Draft, 6/25/75 (Box 17)
    - 162509 - Coffee, Tea or Gloria - Revised Final Draft, 6/30/75; 2 copies (Box 17)
    - 162503 - Queen's Rook Club - Revised Final Draft, 7/18/75 (Box 17)
    - 162504 - Arise Maxine, Arise - Final Draft, 7/24/75 (Box 17)
    - 162501 - M is for Mother - Final Draft, 8/15/75 (Box 17)
    - Premise Notions and 1/2 hr. Budget, 9/17/75 (Box 17)
    - 162511 - Mixed Doubles - Final Draft, 9/19/75; 2 copies (Box 17)
    - 162511 - Mixed Doubles - Revised Final Draft, 9/24/75; 2 copies (Box 17)
    - 162510 - I Want Nancy! - Final Draft, 9/16/75 (Box 17)
    - 162510 - I Want Nancy! - Revised Final Draft, 9/25/75 (Box 17)
  - Here We Go Again
    - 45109 - Sunday Soggy Sunday - Final Draft, 6/7/72 (Box 17)
    - 45113 - Bedfellows Make Strange Politics - Revised, 8/8/72 (Box 17)
  - Hit the Road
    - [no title] (Box 17)
  - Hogan Family
    See also Videos: Hogan Family, below.
    - 44-6351 - California Dreaming - Shooting Script, 8/6/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6352 - California Dreamin' Part 2 - Shooting Script, 8/6/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6353 - Play's the Thing - Shooting Script, 8/23/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6354 - Baby Stops Here - Shooting Script, 8/30/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6355 - From Russia With Fries - Shooting Script, 9/13/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6356 - Ex Marks the Spot - Shooting Script, 9/19/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6357 - It Happened One Night - Or Did It? - Shooting Script, 9/27/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6358 - Best of Friends, Worst of Times - Shooting Script, 10/10/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6359 - Come Fly With Me - Shooting Script, 10/18/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6360 - A Sneaking Suspicion - Shooting Script, 10/25/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6361 - Ho, Ho, Hogans - Shooting Script, 11/7/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6362 - A Family Affair - Shooting Script, 11/14/90 (Box 18)
    - 44-6363 - Isn't It Romantic? - Shooting Script, 11/29/90 (Box 18)
  - Home Sweet Homework
    - [no title] (Box 18)
  - I Dream of Jeannie
    - 411206 - 15 Years Later - Second Draft, 2/12/85 (Box 18)
    - 411206 - 15 Years Later - Revised Final Draft, 4/9/85 (Box 19)
    - 411206 - 15 Years Later - Production Notes, 4/12/85 (Box 19)
  - In the Name of Love
    - Pilot Episode - Second Draft, 1/27/83 (Box 19)
  - Jetsons
    - Space Race (Box 19)
  - Kangaroos in the Kitchen
    - Pilot Script- Revised Final Draft, 4/14/82 (Box 19)
  - Love Nest
    - 01-0643-9490 - Ned's Brother - First Draft, 7/9/74 (Box 19)
    - Story #2 - Wedding Gift - Final Draft, 9/25/74 (Box 19)
    - Story #3 - Dickie's Triangle - Final Draft, 9/26/74 (Box 19)
    - Story #4 - Pinch - Final Draft, 10/14/74 (Box 19)
  - Mason
    - Pilot Script (Box 19)
    - Pilot Script - Final Revised Draft, 3/4/75 (Box 19)
    - Filmways Memo & Rehearsal Schedule, 3/31/75 (Box 19)
    - Pilot Script - First Revision, 4/1/75 (Box 19)
    - Pilot Script - Second Revision w/ change pgs., 4/5/75 (Box 19)
    - Pilot Script - Revised [Third?], 4/6/75 (Box 19)
    - Now We Are Three, 1/20/76 (Box 20)
  - Maude
    - 0113 - Walter's Dilemma - Final Draft, 10/26/72 (Box 20)